<blog>
<post>
        <id>1</id>
        <date>March 9, 2023</date>
        <author>Siya Patel</author>
        <title>What Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania End Credits Set Up</title>
        <summary>
            <image_path>https://fangirlblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Quantumania--800x445.jpg</image_path>
            <text>However, the end-credits especially have given the audience a great amount of insight into what we can expect in future Marvel projects. Let’s take a look at what the post-credits instill for the future of Phase 5!</text>
        </summary>
        <body>Fans of comic books will recognize this image from the opening post-credits scene. Rama-Tut, Immortus, and a variant who seems to be a play on the Scarlet Centurion have a short conversation before the scene quickly shifts to reveal an arena filled to the brim with Kangs from various timelines, with more appearing at an alarming rate.

This first post-credit scene serves two main purposes. “The first is to illustrate the scope of what Ant-Man’s Kang the Conqueror — and Loki’s He Who Remains before him — meant when he said he was standing between their timeline and his infinite variants who meant to destroy it” (IGN). The character of Kang from Ant-Man operates under a philosophy akin to that of Thanos, adamant that he is not out to conquer reality itself but only its many variations and the fragmented histories from which they originated. But his opponents make it very plain that they are simply interested in annihilation, regardless of how mistaken their motives may be.</body>
    </post>
    <post>
        <id>2</id>
        <date>March 16 2023</date>
        <author>Josh Stedman</author>
        <title>The Greatest (Most Successful) Athletes of All-Time</title>
        <summary>
            <image_path>https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/58ee0b551e5b6c8ff18b94ad/1613127047947-LDRW2T3VBA22LVK4K6GX/Michael+Jordan+GOAT.jpg?format=1000w</image_path>
            <text>The 5 Greatest Sporting Athletes Ever: The GOAT debate continues!
Who are the most successful athletes ever?</text>
        </summary>
        <body>The awards they receive throughout their career certainly is a big part of their perceived success. Some athletes aren’t happy with just getting awards. They will strive to enhance the reputation of their sport, as well as their influences on society and the fight for equality. 
The five athletes I’m about to discuss are the athletes I believe have been the most successful. I must also stress this is no particular order and I’m sure everyone will have their own opinion.
Tiger Woods (Golf)A controversial start to the list but despite his rather public flaws, Tiger Woods dominated golf for a long period. Tiger was a sporting icon and is still an instantly recognisable face, even if it is not always for the right reasons.
Tiger Wood’s Early Career
Woods’ talent was there from a young age. On TV show Good Morning America, Woods showed off his talent to the nation. Whilst at University, Woods won various amateur U.S. golf titles before turning pro in 1996. Golfing glory was soon to follow. Aged 21, Woods won the US Masters at Augusta in 1997, with a record score of 270. Not only was he the youngest person to earn the title, but he was also the first African American. The following years saw Woods pick up four U.S. PGA titles, three U.S. Open wins, three Open Championship wins, and three U.S. Masters wins
        </body>
    </post>
        <post>
            <id>3</id>
            <date>April 24,2023</date>
            <author>Felicia Wu</author>
            <title>My first layoff was the best thing that happened to my career</title>
            <summary>
                <image_path>https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/format:webp/1*igYnI1rfUUrry4t1xjUZgA.jpeg</image_path>
                <text>I expect the recent layoff to be no different. Here’s the approach I’m
                    taking for the best that’s yet to come.</text>
            </summary>
            <body>I, along with thousands of others, was impacted by Meta’s layoffs last
                week. This is the second time I experienced a layoff. The first time happened in
                2014 when 40% of my organization at Cisco was cut. Cisco had been conducting
                layoffs every year for a number of years prior to that. I was one of the very
                few technical writers whose main responsibility was designing the user interface
                text in the Cisco WebEx Meetings products. I was also leading Cisco’s product
                dictionary which governed the terminology, voice and tone, style guidelines, and
                localization across all of Cisco’s collaboration technology products. I learned
                on the web that the trailblazing work I was happily doing was called content
                strategy or UX writing. When the layoffs caught up with me, I was relieved. I
                had been secretly hoping I would be next because I felt stuck after having
                worked on the same products for 12 years (6 years on user documentation and
                another 6 years on UX writing). I had tried looking for other opportunities but
                just wasn’t very active because I still had a job. I thought this would be a
                good change. This feeling of relief was quickly eclipsed by shame and guilt. I
                started to speculate why I was selected, and why another person on the team was
                not. I’d gotten promotions and raises throughout the years. Maybe I wasn’t good
                enough after all, I thought. With all the free time, I chaperoned my daughter
                and her class on a field trip during the week. I met some parents for the first
                time. One parent asked me, “What do you do?” “I’m umm… in between jobs,” I said.
                A few days into the new job, I was busy learning about the product. My UX
                instinct kicked in. I started sharing my observations and thoughts about the
                product experiences, the design, and the wording and asked a lot of questions.
                It raised some eyebrows. My manager had a talk with me in a conference room.
                “People here keep a low profile,” she said. It dawned on me that I signed up for
                the wrong job. I made a mistake. I should have known better from doing UX work
                for the past 6 years. What I missed terribly were discussing and scoping
                problems, iterating on solutions, and geeking out voice and tone and UI content.
                I was no longer satisfied with just describing the UIs and writing instructions.
                So, after the first week, I quit. This incident affirmed my passion for product
                development and UX writing. I leaned into my network for companies that might be
                interested in hiring a UX writer. Some of the product designers I had the
                pleasure to work with at Cisco had left Cisco for [24]7.ai. They proposed to the
                Design leadership that they needed a UX writer, and connected me with the
                opportunity. I interviewed with the Chief Design Officer, got an offer, and
                accepted it. I carved out a space for the UX writing discipline at [24]7.ai. A
                year into this role, I became a manager hiring UX writers in the Philippines,
                India, and the U.S. Content design leadership was rewarding and energizing to
                me. I continued on to build and grow a team from the ground up at Clover and
                eventually joined Meta to lead teams that were solving problems on a much
                broader scope. The layoff from nearly 9 years ago pushed me to a whole new
                level. A place that I could not have reached had I not taken the time to
                reflect, listen to my inner voice, and course correct. — — — — — — — — — — — — —
                — — — — — — — — — — — — — — — — — — — Today, it still sucks to be told that my
                position is no longer needed. What’s different is that I now embrace the
                challenge and potential opportunities the layoff brings. Here’s how I’m going to
                apply the lessons I’ve learned to this transition. If you’ve also recently been
                impacted by layoffs, I hope they’re helpful to you. Keep networking and learning
                I love being inspired by connecting with others and learning from them. To me,
                networking and learning can be manifested through an act of service or simply
                engaging with a community of people on the regular basis. I’m also continuing to
                serve as a lead in the UX Writing Leadership Guild. We are an international
                group of senior practitioners and leaders in content design. Contact me if you
                want to know more or join us. Connections can happen in unexpected ways. A
                former Design colleague who was also impacted by the layoffs reached out to me
                on LinkedIn. We both agreed that we could teach each other some things, so we’re
                going to grab a virtual coffee and just chat and support each other. Interacting
                with others gives me strengths during weird times such as this. If you’re shying
                away from people because you’re still feeling emotional about the job loss,
                that’s totally understandable. At least surround yourself with positive people.

            </body>
        </post>
    </blog>